Indrakant Mandal

Delhi, Delhi indrakantmandal5_ffr@indeedemail.com 9582418671

To Acquire A Challenging Position In An Environment Where I Can Best Utilize My Working Experience, Skills And Education. Play a direct role in the unlimited growth and success of solid organization.

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

Work Experience

Assistant Manager (ERP Software)

Espire Group January 2020 to Present

Student

Bharati Vidyapeeth, Institute of Mgt. & Research December 2012 to December 2019

ERP Software In charge Dec 2012 to Dec 2019

Key Skills and Roles performed by me

- > Software Management and Implementation
- ♦ ERP and CRM Software of Academics modules
- 1) Academic: Student all activates managed online (Dashboard) like Profile Management, Subject Management, Time Table Creations & updating, Attendance Mgt., Short Attendance Letter, SMS, Internal e-mail, Online feedback and query management.
- 2) HR: Online Leave Management System, Teaching and Non-Teaching Profile Management, Assign Lecture and Work Mgt., Daily Attendance, Leave Details, and salary management.
- 3) Training & Placement:- To maintain company profile, Online registration process and resume collections system from students, students placements records etc.
- 4) Fee Management:- Students Fee dues creations and submission of fee and generate report according to administrations need.
- 5) Hostel Management:- Online Advance booking System, Student Room allocation, Daily Attendance, Feedback and grievance management etc.
- 6) Library Management:- Online OPAC Systems for all students and faculty members, Barcode and thumb based Issue return process, Book, Magazine details management systems
- 7) Examination:-Student Subject allocation, Internal and university online marks mgt. system, Exam room seating planning, exam attendance student's backlog records and result published etc.
- 8) Alumni: Course wise passed students details keeping, keep in touch through dashboard interactions through alumni meet and participants through many academic event.
- 9) Feedback & No Dues System: A transparent platform created for stack holder (Students, Faculty members and Parents) to give their feedback for making strong system. Online No dues System where students can take NOC from all concern Department.

- Database Management and Administration
- > SQL Database installation, configuration and management
- > SSRS
- > SQL Query optimizations
- > MS Access Database management
- > Restore and backup of database
- > User Permission grant and role management.
- > User activity Monitor
- Computer Hardware and Networking
- > PC and Server configuration and setup for ready to use
- ➤ Printer Setup
- ➤ LAN and Wi-Fi Setup
- > General troubleshooting of pc and networks
- Sever setup and management
- > Windows Server Installation and Setup
- > IIS Server
- > DHCP
- > File Server
- > Proxy Server
- Web application and software Programming Skills
- > Website Design and Maintenance
- ➤ ASP.NET
- > HTML, DHTML, XML
- > CSS
- > JAVA SCRIPT
- > C, C++
- ➤ Visual Basic and dot Net
- ➤ Core Java
- ➤ PHP
- Cloud Computing Services and application used
- ➤ Microsoft Azure Setup (AZ-103)
- ➤ Office 365
- > Google Sheet, Docs, Slides, Forms etc.
- General Software used in offices and by Management
- > MS -Word, MS- Excel, MS-Power Point, MS-Outlook.
- > MIS Reporting.
- ➤ Power BI

Education

B.Tech

Rajasthan Vidyapeeth University 2012

Diploma in Technical Education

State Board

2008

Bihar School Examination Board 2002

College & University